// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Who invented C++??",
    answer: "Bjarne Stroustrup",
    options: [
      "Dennis Ritchie",
      "Ken Thompson",
      "Bjarne Stroustrup",
      "Brian Kernighan"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which of the following is the correct syntax of including a user defined header files in C++?",
    answer: "#include “userdefined”",
    options: [
      "#include [userdefined]",
      "#include “userdefined”",
      "#include studio.h",
      "#include <userdefined>"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Which of the following user-defined header file extension used in c++?",
    answer: "h",
    options: [
      "hg",
      "cpp",
      "hs",
      "h"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Which of the following is not a type of Constructor in C++?",
    answer: "Friend constructor",
    options: [
      "Friend constructor",
      "Default constructor",
      "Parameterized constructor",
      "Copy constructor"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which of the following approach is used by C++?",
    answer: "Bottom-up",
    options: [
      "Left-right",
      "Right-left",
      "Bottom-up",
      "Top-down"
    ]
  },
  

  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Which of the following type is provided by C++ but not C?",
    answer: "bool",
    options: [
      "double",
      "float",
      "int",
      "bool"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "By default, all the files in C++ are opened in _________ mode.",
    answer: "Text",
    options: [
      "Binary",
      "VTC",
      "Text",
      "ISCII"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Which of the following correctly declares an array in C++?",
    answer: "int array[10];",
    options: [
      "array{10};",
      "int array[10];",
      "array array[10];",
      "int array;"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which is more effective while calling the C++ functions?",
    answer: "call by reference",
    options: [
      "call by reference",
      "call by pointer",
      "call by object",
      "call by value"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "What is Inheritance in C++?",
    answer: "Deriving new classes from existing classes",
    options: [
      "Overloading of classes",
      "Classes with same names",
      "Deriving new classes from existing classes",
      "Wrapping of data into a single class"
    ]
  },
  
];